Reginald Mosley

1422 Pennick Road Brunswick GA 31525

(770) 828-6724

rmosley241@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I have performed various professional duties over the years and have grown with each new experience. I see every workplace as a challenge to embrace, and I look forward to any opportunity to gain a new skill, meet new people, and increase my effectiveness as a staff member. It is in my nature to be fair, while also maintaining the standards of my employer in a leadership capacity. In my time at the Federal Law Enforcement Training Center (FLETC), I have gained a deep understanding of FLETC's essential role in the nation's Homeland Security framework, as well as the various training programs that form its core. I have had the privilege to work closely with the many agencies that populate the facility, and respect their unique missions that ensure our country's safety.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Quality Control Inspector, BPA Facilities Services (FLETC) Glynco, GA 2018-Present

In this position I assumed a management role for the student housing contract on FLETC. I am responsible for six buildings and a staff of over 40 employees.

Duties and Accomplishments -My primary function is to ensure contract compliance with FLETC guidelines. In service of that I perform various essential functions:

- Work in conjunction with FLETC Contract Compliance Specialists to resolve any issues they come across during facility inspections
- Conduct daily inspections to ensure that all buildings meet FLETC's standards
- Effectively communicate company/FLETC policies with contract employees
- Ensure that occupational safety best practices are observed per OSHA guidelines
- Addressing student requests and complaints in a timely manner
- Manage student and government property, including participating in surveys of damaged government property and abandoned student property
- Inform students of potential FLETC housing policy violations and notify Contract Compliance Specialists if issues persist.
- Resolve employee disputes in conjunction with the contract's Project Manager
- Notify my superior of any inventory deficiencies for my 5 buildings; take and review deliveries from suppliers as needed

Roleplayer, Omni Corporation

Brunswick, GA — 2014-2022

In this position I perform a variety of roles in training scenarios at the Federal Law Enforcement Center. A dedication to delivering a consistent performance has been my focus and allowed me to be commended on my hard work on several occasions.

Accomplishments

 I am trusted to perform the duties of Lead Roleplayer on numerous occasions, and maintain the respect of my peers. I strive to be both firm and fair, and have worked to resolve issues while managing various personalities

- Developing warm relationships with the various FLETC instructors I encountered on a daily basis, especially those within Enforcement Operations, Investigative Operations, Behavior Sciences and Air Force Office of Special Investigations.
- I gained a comprehensive knowledge of the various locations within FLETC, having worked in every possible training environment at the center.

Bartender/Server, Sea Island Company (Tavola)

Saint Simons Island 2011-2014

In this position, I was required to provide a 5-star experience in the often stressful world of fine dining. I developed intrapersonal skills there that have served me to this day.

Accomplishments

- I was required to mentally organize large amounts of information, to serve a demanding clientele that expected excellence
- I was tasked with managing bar inventory to ensure adequate levels during all times, including generating resupply orders.
- I was a member of a team of restaurants that helped ensure Sea Island was awarded a Forbes 5-star rating for each year that I worked there
- This was my first exposure to the various personality types that you
 encounter in the workplace, and I was seen as a reliable and honest
 co-worker and employee who took pride in his work.
- I was commended on my service by numerous guests, which reflected well on my unit, and the resort as a whole

Tech Services/Sales, Office Depot

Brunswick, GA 2007

My first official work experience, I learned a great deal about how to troubleshoot problems and maintain an orderly work environment. I worked in the technology section and stockroom, which each had unique challenges. Additionally, I gained an awareness of proper inventory procedures.

Accomplishments

- I posted the highest number of sales of desktop and laptop PCs for each month that I worked
- I was responsible for explaining pieces of technology to customers and also troubleshooting their issues should they have any questions after a purchase.
- I was offered a position of Assistant Manager, shortly before returning to college

EDUCATION

Georgia Tech Full-Stack Web Development Program (MERN stack)

January 2023-July 2023

North Carolina Central University

2006-2008

Union Grove High School

2002-2006

SKILLS

Long-term Contract Compliance Experience Inventory Management Telework Ready Home Office and Computer Comprehensive Knowledge of the FLETC Campus Typing: 90-100 WPM Basic Spanish Fast Learner Strong Work Ethic

REFERENCES

Available upon request.